BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.3690: American Machine and Foundry Co. and IAM Local Lodge 992, 1959-1962 (Box 30, Folder 3690)
  - Code no.3691: Clarostat Mfg. Co. Inc. and IUE Local 242, 1959-1963 (Box 30, Folder 3691)
  - Code no.3696: Raytheon Manufacturing Company and IAM Local 1836, 1959-1961 (Box 30, Folder 3696)
  - Code no.3699: Tung-Sol Electric Inc. and IBEW Local 1497, 1961-1967 (Box 30, Folder 3699)
  - Code no.3700: Tung-Sol Electric Inc. and Local 433 Independent Union, 1959-1967 (Box 30, Folder 3700)
  - Code no.3702: Electric Storage Battery Company and UAW Local 934, 1206, 88, 509, 1959-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3702)
  - Code no.3711: Philco Corporation and Radio and Television Workers Local 102, 1961-1967 (Box 30, Folder 3711)
  - Code no.3716: General Electric Company, Hotpoint Business Operations and Sheet Metal Workers International Association Local 571, 1963-1973 (Box 30, Folder 3716)
  - Code no.3718: Crouse-Hinds Company and IBEW Local 2084, 1963-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3718)
  - Code no.3719: Borg-Warner Corporation, Norge Division and Allied Industrial Workers Local 370, 1962-1966 (Box 30, Folder 3719)
  - Code no.3721: Western Electric Company, Inc., Kansas City Works and CWA, 1964-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3721)
  - Code no.3723: P.R. Mallory and Co., Inc. and IUE Local 1001, 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 3723)
  - Code no.3736: Western Electric Company, Inc., Shreveport Works and IBEW Local 2188, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3736)
  - Code no.3737: Rauland Corporation of Chicago and IBEW Local 1031, 1964-1967 (Box 31, Folder 3739)
  - Code no.3749: Zenith Radio Corporation of Missouri and IBEW Local 453, 1968-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3749)
  - Code no.3760: Teletype Corporation and IBEW Local 2022, 1969-1971 (Box 31, Folder 3760)
  - Code no.3773: Western Electric Company, Inc., Denver Works and IBEW, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3773)
  - Code no.3782: General Motors Corporation and IUE-CLC, 1967-1971 (Box 31, Folder 3782)
  - Code no.3797: Western Electric Company, Inc. Lisle Plant and IBEW Local 2310, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3797)
  - Code no.4004: Bendix-Westinghouse Automotive Air Brake Co. and UAW Local 971, 1958-1971 (Box 31, Folder 4004)
  - Code no.4006: Budd Company and UAW Locals 92, 306, 813, 1122, 1961-1968 (Box 31, Folder 4006)
  - Code no.4007: Chrysler Corporation and UAW, 1961-1967 (Box 31, Folder 4007)
  - Code no. 4010: Chrysler Corporation and the UAW, Local 212, 230, 412, 1284, 1961-1971 (Box 31, Folder 4010)
  - Code no.4011: Chrysler Corporation and UAW Local 624, 1961-1965 (Box 31, Folder 4011)
  - Code no.4015: Dana Corporation and UAW Local 1501, 1967-1973 (Box 31, Folder 4015)
  - Code no.4017: Eaton Yale and Towne, Inc. and UAW, 1967-1973 (Box 31, Folder 4017)
  - Code no.4019: Ford Motor Company and UAW, 1967-1970 (Box 31, Folder 4019)
  - Code no.4020: Fruehauf Trailer Company and Allied Industrial Workers of America Local 925, 1959-1970 (Box 31, Folder 4020)
  - Code no.4038: North American Rockwell Corporation and United Steelworkers of America Locals 2143, 3261, 4051, 4194, 2646, 1971- 1974 (Box 32, Folder 4038)
  - Code no.4039: A.O. Smith Corporation and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers Local 575, 1959-1964 (Box 32, Folder 4039)
  - Code no.4040: A.O. Smith Corporation and Smith Steel Workers Local 19806, 1959-1968 (Box 32, Folder 4040)
  - Code no.4041: Studebaker-Packard Corporation and UAW, 1958-1961 (Box 32, Folder 4041)
  - Code no.4042: Thompson Ramo Wooldridge Corp. and UAW Local 247, 1961-1970 (Box 32, Folder 4042)
  - Code no.4045: White Motor Company, White Division and UAW Local 32, 1961-1971 (Box 32, Folder 4045)
  - Code no.4048: Avco Corporation, Avco Lycoming Division and UAW Local 1010, 1967-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4048)
  - Code no.4049: Beech Aircraft Corporation and IAM, 1960-1969 (Box 32, Folder 4049)
  - Code no.4050: Bell Helicopter Company and UAW Local 218, 1960-1966 (Box 32, Folder 4050)
  - Code no.4051: Eclipse Machine Division and UAW Local 604, 1958-1961 (Box 32, Folder 4051)
  - Code no.4055: Boeing Company and Seattle Professional Engineering Employees Association, 1968-1974 (Box 32, Folder 4055)
  - Code no.4056: Boeing Airplane Company and IAM Lodge 751, 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 4056)
  - Code no.4057: Boeing Company, Vertol Division and UAW Local 1069, 1960-1968 (Box 32, Folder 4057)
  - Code no.4107: Manufacturers and Repairers Association of New Orleans and New Orleans Metal Trades Council, 1960-1963 (Box 32, Folder 4107)
  - Code no.4113: Sun Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers Local 802, 1961-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4113)
  - Code no.4114: Todd Shipyards Corporation and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 9, 1959- 1965 (Box 32, Folder 4114)
  - Code no.4126: Lansing Division, White Motor Company and UAW Local 650, 1961-1967 (Box 32, Folder 4126)
  - Code no.4127: General Electric Company and UAW Local 647, 1960-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4127)
  - Code no.4144: General Dynamics/Electric Boat and Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 5, 1969- 1974 (Box 32, Folder 4144)
  - Code no.4146: Midland-Ross Corporation and UAW of America Local 486, 1961-1967 (Box 32, Folder 4146)
  - Code no.4148: Harley-Davidson Motor Co. and Allied Industrial Workers Local 209, 1966-1970 (Box 32, Folder 4148)
  - Code no.4161: Shipyard Industry of San Diego and IAM Local Lodge 389, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 4161)
  - Code no.4167: Schwinn Bicycle Company and Schwinn Employees Shop Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 4167)
  - Code no.4186: Stewart-Warner Corporation and IBEW Local 1031, 1957-1962 (Box 32, Folder 4186)
  - Code no.4405: Ametek, Inc., U.S. Gauge Division and IAM Lodge 1092, 1967-1972 (Box 33, Folder 4405)
  - Code no.4409: Minneapolis Honeywell Regulator Co. and IBT Local 1145, 1960-1966 (Box 33, Folder 4409)
  - Code no.4410: Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Company, Grayson Controls Division and UAW Local 805, 1960-1968 (Box 33, Folder 4410)
  - Code no.4412: Robertshaw-Fulton Controls Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1969 (Box 33, Folder 4412)
  - Code no.4422: United States Time Corporation and IAM Lodge 921, 1961-1971 (Box 33, Folder 4422)
  - Code no.4424: Johnson and Johnson and TWUA Local 1437, 1962-1972 (Box 33, Folder 4424)
  - Code no.4426: Fischer and Porter Company and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, 1963-1967 (Box 33, Folder 4426)
  - Code no.4426: Alloy Steel Casting Company and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, 1963-1967 (Box 33, Folder 4426)
  - Code no.4607: National Association of Doll Manufacturers, Inc. and Toy and Novelty Workers of America Local 223, 1960-1967 (Box 33, Folder 4607)
  - Code no.4608: A.G. Spalding and Bros., Inc. and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers Local 1851, 1960-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4608)
  - Code no.4616: Louis Marx and Co. of West Virginia and United Toy Workers Union Local 149, 1964-1971 (Box 33, Folder 4616)
- Series VII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
  - Code no.314: Illinois Association of Breweries and Beer, Liquor and Soft Drinks Union Local 744, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 314)
  - Code no.314: Chicago Beer Wholesalers Association and Beer, Liquor and Soft Drinks Union Local 744, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 314)
  - Code no.6400: Building Materials Dealers of Greater Cleveland and Excavating, Building Material, Construction Drivers, and Race Track Employers Local 436, 1959-1974 (Box 35, Folder 6400)
  - Code no.8318: Rock Products and Ready Mix Concrete Employers of So. California and Teamsters Locals 420, 692, 495, 88, 982, 871, 235, 1961-1967 (Box 36, Folder 8318)
- Series VIII: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.214: Meat Trade Institute, Inc. and Butchers' Union of Greater New York and New Jersey Local 174, 1961-1969 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Meat Trade Institute, Inc. and Butchers' Union of Greater New York and New Jersey Local 174, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Agreement effective 6/15/1961 and expires on 4/15/1964. Covers an unknown number of workers in NY; NJ
      Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
    - Item 2: Meat Trade Institute, Inc. and Butchers' Union of Greater New York and New Jersey Local 174, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 6/16/1966 and expires on 6/15/1969. Covers an unknown number of workers in NY; NJ
  - Code no.237: Milk Dealers of Philadelphia and Vicinity and Food Driver Salesmen Dairy and Ice Cream Workers Union Local 463, 1959- 1968 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Milk Dealers of Philadelphia and Vicinity and Food Driver Salesmen Dairy and Ice Cream Workers Union Local 463, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1959 and expires on 9/30/1962. Covers 4500 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 2: Milk Dealers of Philadelphia and Vicinity and Food Driver Salesmen Dairy and Ice Cream Workers Union Local 463, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1962 and expires on 9/30/1965. Covers 4500 workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Code no.280: Retail Baking Companies in New York, NY and Cake Bakers Union Local 51, 1959-1965 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Retail Baking Companies in New York, NY and Cake Bakers Union Local 51, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1959 and expires on 1/31/1962. Covers 1200 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 2: Retail Baking Companies in New York, NY and Cake Bakers Union Local 51, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1962 and expires on 1/31/1965. Covers 1300 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 3: Retail Baking Companies in New York, NY and Cake Bakers Union Local 51, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Code no.286: Retail Bakery Employers' Council of Greater New York and Bakery and Confectionery Workers Local 3, 1956-1968 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Retail Bakery Employers' Council of Greater New York and Bakery and Confectionery Workers Local 3, 1956-1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1956 and expires on 1/31/1959. Covers 1500 workers in New York
    - Item 2: Retail Bakery Employers' Council of Greater New York and Bakery and Confectionery Workers Local 3, 1962-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1962 and expires on 1/31/1962. Covers 5000 workers in New York
    - Item 3: Retail Bakery Employers' Council of Greater New York and Bakery and Confectionery Workers Local 3, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1965 and expires on 1/31/1968. Covers 5000 workers in New York
  - Code no.6703: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 427, 1959- 1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 427, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 8/30/1959 and expires on 9/3/1961. Covers 3600 workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 2: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 427, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 9/4/1961 and expires on 9/1/1963. Covers 3200 workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 3: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 427, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 9/2/1963 and expires on 9/4/1965. Covers 3700 workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 4: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 427, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 9/4/1965 and expires on 9/1/1968. Covers 4200 workers in Cleveland, OH
  - Code no.6706: First National Store, Inc. and New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1960- 1967 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: First National Store, Inc. and New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 2/8/1960 and expires on 2/10/1962. Covers 9000 workers in New England
    - Item 2: First National Store, Inc. and New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 2/12/1962 and expires on 8/8/1964. Covers 9000 workers in New England
    - Item 3: First National Store, Inc. and New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/10/1964 and expires on 11/12/1966. Covers 12000 workers in New England
    - Item 4: First National Store, Inc. and New England Council of Meat Cutters, Butchers, Food Store and Allied Workers, 1966-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 11/14/1966 and expires on 11/11/1967. Covers 9000 workers in New England
  - Code no.6765: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 421, 1955-1970 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 421, 1955-1956; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 11/7/1955 and expires on 11/4/1956. Covers 4100 workers in Los Angeles, CA
    - Item 2: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 421, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 11/2/1959 and expires on 11/1/1964. Covers 4000 workers in Los Angeles, CA
    - Item 3: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 421, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 12/18/1964 and expires on 11/4/1967. Covers 3800 workers in Los Angeles, CA
    - Item 4: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 421, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 11/6/1967 and expires on 11/7/1970. Covers 6638 workers in Los Angeles, CA
  - Code no.7300: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1959-1969 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 6/2/1959 and expires on 6/1/1964. Covers 2900 workers in Hollywood, CA
    - Item 2: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Item 3: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1962-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1962 and expires on 6/30/1963. Covers 2900 workers in Hollywood, CA
    - Item 4: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1963-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1963 and expires on 6/30/1964. Covers 2500 workers in Hollywood, CA
    - Item 5: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1961-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1961 and expires on 6/30/1966. Covers 210 workers in San Diego, CA
    - Item 6: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1961-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1961 and expires on 6/30/1966. Covers an unknown number of workers in Colton, CA
    - Item 7: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1961-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Item 8: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1961-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1961 and expires on 6/30/1966. Covers an unknown number of workers in Hollywood, CA
    - Item 9: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1961-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Item 10: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1964-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1964 and expires on 6/30/1969. Covers an unknown number of workers in Los Angeles, CA
    - Item 11: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1964-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Item 12: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1964-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Item 13: Retail Drug Store Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1964-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6712: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1959-1964 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1959 and expires on 3/31/1964. Covers an unknown number of workers in Los Angeles, CA
    - Item 2: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6714: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Food Clerks Union Local 1245, 1960-1969 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Food Clerks Union Local 1245, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 2/29/1960 and expires on 9/2/1962. Covers 1750 workers in Pennsylvania
    - Item 2: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Food Clerks Union Local 1245, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1962 and expires on 8/29/1965. Covers 1750 workers in Pennsylvania
    - Item 3: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Food Clerks Union Local 1245, 1965-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 8/29/1965 and expires on 9/3/1966. Covers 1700 workers in Pennsylvania
    - Item 4: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Food Clerks Union Local 1245, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 9/4/1966 and expires on 9/27/1969. Covers 1750 workers in Pennsylvania
  - Code no.6715: Food Industry, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1105, 1959-1971 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Food Industry, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1105, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1959 and expires on 4/1/1961. Covers 2700 workers in Washington
    - Item 2: Food Industry, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1105, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1961 and expires on 4/1/1964. Covers 3300 workers in Washington
    - Item 3: Food Industry, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1105, 1964-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1964 and expires on 4/1/1968. Covers 2500 workers in Washington
    - Item 4: Food Industry, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union Local 1105, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1968 and expires on 4/1/1971. Covers 5500 workers in Washington
  - Code no.6716: Food Industry, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 81, 1959-1964 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Food Industry, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 81, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1959 and expires on 10/1/1961. Covers 2200 workers in King,WA; Kitsap WA
    - Item 2: Food Industry, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 81, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Item 3: Food Industry, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America Local 81, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1961 and expires on 10/1/1964. Covers 2200 workers in King,WA; Kitsap WA
  - Code no.6720: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1959-1968 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 9/6/1959 and expires on 9/9/1961. Covers 2379 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 9/10/1961 and expires on 9/8/1963. Covers 2379 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 3: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 9/8/1963 and expires on 9/12/1965. Covers 3300 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 4: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 590, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 9/13/1965 and expires on 9/15/1968. Covers 2500 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
  - Code no.6723: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Scranton Unit and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 1687, 1393, 1958- 1963 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Scranton Unit and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 1687, 1393, 1958-1960; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 3/30/1958 and expires on 7/30/1960. Covers 2300 workers in Scranton, PA
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Scranton Unit and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 1687, 1393, 1960-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/31/1960 and expires on 1/5/1963. Covers 2000 workers in Scranton, PA
  - Code no.6725: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Paterson Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 464, 1960-1971 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Paterson Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 464, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1960 and expires on 6/2/1962. Covers 6000 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Paterson Unit and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 464, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1962 and expires on 6/2/1964. Covers 4500 workers in New Jersey